upperseeker.com 2014-02-13

# UpperSeeker.com - Internet Advertising Technology

Your online privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we provide a link to it on every page of our website.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices or the [ UpperSeeker](http://upperseeker.com/) website.

**UpperSeeker** provides links to many other websites that are beyond our control. Websites that we link to may have privacy and security policies that differ from **UpperSeeker**. Please understand that we are not responsible, in any manner, for the privacy, security practices, or content of such websites. 

**Types of Information We Collect And How We Use It:**

**IP Addresses  
**We use IP Addresses for statistical and system administration purposes. IP addresses are anonymously logged to track a users session. We do not link IP addresses with any personally identifiable information. This means that a users session will be logged but that user will remain anonymous to us. We can and will us IP address to identify a user when necessary to enforce our terms of service or protect our site, network, advertisers or users.

**Cookies  
****UpperSeeker** uses session cookies to prevent banner network and affiliate system abuse and cheating. This cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information about users.

**UpperSeeker** _does not require a user to accept or use browser cookies. Most web browsers will allow you the option to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept._

**Contact Information  
**We collect contact information (like your name, address, telephone number, email address and URL) through various registration forms, surveys, sweepstakes entry forms. 

This information is used to provide you with services that you requested (like submitting your website to our search engine, joining our link exchange service, or if you order products and services), contact you when necessary, or to send you additional information regarding **UpperSeeker** or selected reputable partners and affiliates.

> **Financial Information  
>  **We collect financial information (like credit card and banking information) from users who order goods, products or services from us
> 
> We will use this information to bill and collect for the goods, products and/or services that you order. We will also use this information to confirm your registration qualifications where appropriate.  
> 

**Specific Information About UpperSeeker Services:**

> **UpperSeeker Affiliate Program  
>  **The Search Index Affiliate Program allows website owners to earn advertising credit for displaying a search box on their website. Users are required to complete an application that includes their names, email address, mailing address, telephone number. Users must also choose a unique username and password. Users are required to place a unique html code on their website that allows **UpperSeeker** to track searches and click-throughs that originate on the affiliate site. **UpperSeeker** uses your information to administer the service that we provide you.

**With Whom Does UpperSeeker Share Information:**

> **UpperSeeker** will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone, except as expressly described below:
> 
> We have your express consent to share your information   
>  We need to share your information to provide you the product or service that you requested.   
>  We believe in good faith that any applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it.   
>  When the disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user.  
> 
> 
> We may share generic, aggregate and anonymous information with advertisers and affiliates 
> 
> **UpperSeeker** does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly. ( **UpperSeeker** will divulge information only as necessary to comply with state and federal laws.)

**Notification of Changes To The Privacy Policy:**

> Our privacy policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.
> 
> If at some point in the future, **UpperSeeker** changes the usage practices that affect any of your personally identifiable information, We will notify you by email of the changes. At the time of that message you will be able to opt-out of this information usage by sending an email message to the following email address: [ support@upperseeker.com](mailto:support@upperseeker.com).

**Choice / Opt-Out Of Promotional and Marketing Communications:**

    If you no longer wish to receive our occasional newsletters or other marketing communications from **UpperSeeker** you may opt-out of receiving these by following the unsubscribe / removal instructions located at the very bottom of these communications or by sending an email to us at [ support@upperseeker.com](mailto:support@upperseeker.com). 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect by editing your account information directly using the appropriate control panel on our website. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes or corrections to any of your personally identifiable information.

**How To Contact Us:**

> If you have any questions about the **UpperSeeker** privacy commitment, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us please contact: [ support@upperseeker.com](mailto:support@upperseeker.com).
